twitpic.com 2012-12-14

# Twitpic - Share photos and videos on Twitter

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 1, 2008.**

Twitpic Inc. (“Twitpic”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Twitpic website located at www.twitpic.com and any linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by Twitpic in connection therewith (the “Site”) and using Twitpic services (the “Services”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Twitpic does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access though Twitpic, or to individuals that Twitpic does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collected Upon Registration

If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to Twitpic. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that you decide to include in your public profile. 

### Additional Information 

Your full user name and your photo, if you decide to upload one, are displayed to people on the Twitpic Site. Once a member, you may provide additional information in the profile section, including but not limited to your bio, your location, as well as your personal web site, if you have one. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional. 

### Log Data

When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service 

### Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Twitpic may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our Service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

We may allow advertisers, third party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisements directly to you within Twitpic's Sites, Services and Software. By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer and trigger their own Web beacons. If you would like to contact the advertisers, third party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies with which we have relationships to learn more about their privacy policies and what options (if any) they offer to opt out of their data collection, please visit their web site(s). Some of these companies are participants in the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. You can learn more about NAI and how you may "opt out" of targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

In addition, to trigger certain cookies, we may pass an encrypted or “hashed” (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your twitter ID to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, those cookies. If you prefer not to receive interest based content and advertisements, or do not wish to enable other services which make use of Twitpic data, you can always opt-out by clicking [here](http://www.privacychoice.org/choose). After you opt-out, Twitpic will not enable or serve interest-based content and targeted advertisements or enable the other services. Please note that opting-out does not turn off other advertisements. Also, if you change your computer, change your internet browser (e.g. from Internet Explorer to Firefox), or delete all your cookies, you will need to renew your preferences. 

### Web Site Tracking, Reporting

Many of our web pages also contain special electronic images (called a "single-pixel gif" or "gifs") that allow us to gather only non-personally identifiable traffic statistics and other aggregate information about visitors to our sites. Twitpic (through itself or third parties) uses this technology to collect and accumulate anonymous data that helps us understand and analyze the experience of people visiting our web sites and, along with other information you provide, customize your future visits and improve our web sites. Please keep in mind that none of this information is personally identifiable. 

### Banner Ads

The Services may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider. The ad service provider may place or utilize their own unique cookie on your browser, and may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. Twitpic is not responsible for the collection of these cookies and is not responsible for the actions of the ad service providers. Twitpic does not sponsor, endorse or guarantee any products or services advertised by third parties on its site. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Information about our users is important to our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below. 

### Service Providers

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data. 

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

### Information You Post

When you post a pic through Twitpic, information about you, including user profile information, may be visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, that information becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others and redistributed through the internet and other media channels. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Twitpic, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Twitpic goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Twitpic may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Twitpic cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Twitpic or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 

### Non-US Users

If you are not a resident of the United States, you understand and agree that Twitpic stores and processes your information on computers located in the United States, and by providing any data to Twitpic, you consent to the transfer of such information to the United States. 

### Security Precautions

Twitpic has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Your information may be transferred to and maintained in whole or in part on computer networks which may be located outside of the state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction in which you reside, and may be stored on equipment or in facilities leased or licensed from third parties. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and make all commercially reasonable efforts to do so, Twitpic cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. This privacy policy does not apply to any information, including such photographs, that you submit for use in publicly available areas. We ask that you do not submit any personal information, including contact information or financial information, for display in public areas, as other people who use the Services will see it. If you submit such information for display in public areas, Twipic cannot prevent it from being used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information for display in public areas, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed. 

### Links to Other Websites

The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

### Our Policy Towards Children

The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our system. 

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or information that you have submitted to us you can contact us at: 

Email:  
noah@twitpic.com 

Address:  
TwitPic Inc.  
PO Box 22126  
Charleston, SC 29413
